

Juan Pablo Olalde

Spanish • • • •

English • • • •

About me

Argentine,I was born on 2nd of March of 1993 in the city of La Plata,Capital of the province of Buenos Aires. In the year 2010 I finished hi/gh school and started my Computer Engineering education, after a year I changed to Programming, which I completed the first 3 years. In the year 2020, I decided to travel and get to know new cultures.

In 2020 I lived in Copenhagen, Denmark, and in 2021 I moved to Berlin, Germany, where I currently live.

My interests are electronics, programming, renewable energies, sports such as swimming and martial arts. I also enjoy teaching and dancing tango.

Olaldejp@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/JuanPabloOlalde

Education

Beer Course | Fundacion Biosfera | 2022

Skills: Craft beer production

Permaculture Course | https://gaia.org.ar/ | 2021

Skills: Eco Building , Plant care , renewable energys , Responsible land use

and reuse of resources

PC Repair course | University of La Plata | July 2014

Skills: PC assembly & repair

Extra: Teaching seniors an introducing to computer-usage

Computer Engineering | University of La Plata | 2010 - 2011

Skills: Mathematics (I, II and III), Physics, Chemistry and the first subject

of Electronics

High School | University of La Plata | 2010

Orientation in Macro and Micro Economics, Marketing, Company structures

Experience

Gorillas Technologies GmbH | 2021- 2022 | web: gorillas.io/

Operation associate |Bismarckstraße 94, 10625 Berlin, Germany Responsible for quality control and stock of products, designs and complete excel pages

Cafe A | 2020- 2021 | web: https://cafe-a.orderyoyo.com/ Waiter | Herlev Hovedgade 17, 2730 Herlev, Dinamarca

Pejsegaarden | 2021 |

Bartender | Frederikssundsvej 343, 345, 2700 København, Dinamarca Bartender at the event house pejsegaarden, also helping with food and general careting service

La bodeguita BAR | 2014-2016|

Bartender | Diagonal 73 and 49, 1900 La Plata, Argentina Mainly cocktails like daiquiris, mohito, cubalibre and beers

El Boyo pizzas y pastas | 2013-2014|

Comis manager and waiter | Calle 6 1739 , Villa Elisa, Provincia de Buenos Aires, Argentina

As a comis manager, I led a group of 4 people to organize, rearrange the tables and keep the restaurant and all the utensils clean.